{
  "LevelId": 66,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 672,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "ARCHENEMY",
      "question": "entity that is considered the ultimate and most formidable opponent,"
    },
    {
      "id": 673,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "ABBOTSHIP",
      "question": "position or role of an abbey's superior, typically in charge of a monastery or a group of monks"
    },
    {
      "id": 674,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "ANAMNESIS",
      "question": "medicine to describe the recollection or memory of past events,"
    },
    {
      "id": 675,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "AUTOCLAVE",
      "question": "laboratories and medical facilities to sterilize equipment"
    },
    {
      "id": 676,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "ALLIGATOR",
      "question": "a partially armored body is native to areas in the Americas and belongs to the Crocodylia order"
    },
    {
      "id": 677,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "AGGREGATE",
      "question": "elements or particles gathered together into a unified whole"
    },
    {
      "id": 678,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "AKINESIAS",
      "question": "characterized by the loss or impairment of voluntary muscle movements,"
    },
    {
      "id": 679,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "BULLNECKS",
      "question": "describe individuals with a muscular and thick neck,"
    },
    {
      "id": 680,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "BAPTIZERS",
      "question": "individuals or groups who perform the act of baptizing"
    },
    {
      "id": 681,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "BEDIZENED",
      "question": "decorating something, often with excessive or gaudy ornamentation,"
    },
    {
      "id": 682,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "HOMOGENIZE",
      "question": "mixture uniform in composition by blending or mixing its components thoroughly"
    }
  ]
}